(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-04T23:10:27.912685",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
パレード...
Parade...
Parade Parade
輝くんだよ
We're gonna shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With voices calling out to each other as our signal,
Parade Parade Parade
探しにゆく
We set out to search,
スタートは何処だって
no matter where our starting line may be.
ただ 独り言 紡いだ
I simply spun out soliloquies.
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just ran, longing for a beginning.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit up far away in the dark,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
was a name far too dazzling.
それは 優しすぎる思い出
It was a memory far too kind.
もっと近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer,
思いがけず結び合った
and unexpectedly, we connected.
ほら 今 迷子は僕らになった
Look, now "the lost children" became "us."
Parade Parade Parade
輝くんだよ
We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both your frustration and love.
風 夢 羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
A humble prayer is light, an omen without end.
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of.
ここから これから
From here, from now on,
Our Bright Parade Parade
まだ 頼りない予感を
This still-faint premonition,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
let's sing it—there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can unravel,
いつかまた逢えるおまじない
a charm so we'll meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロに始まったストーリー
A story that started from zero that day,
数え切れない言の葉
countless words—
数えるような思いじゃないさ
these aren't feelings meant to be counted.
ほら 今 僕らを一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one.
Parade Parade Parade
美しいんだよ
It's so beautiful!
許し合える切なさ 夜は煌めく
A mutual forgiving sorrow, the night sparkles.
雨 晴れ 枯れ 待ったのない空
Rain, clear skies, withering—an unpausing sky.
相応しい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
The right journey is walking together with you...
君と歩くことなんだ
...it's walking together with you.
ただいまを聞けば
If I hear "I'm home,"
お帰りって叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because none of this is taken for granted.
Parade Parade Parade
輝くんだよ
We're gonna shine!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
Filling the darkness is you, is me!
Parade Parade Parade
輝くんだよ
We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both your frustration and love.
風 夢 羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
A humble prayer is light, an omen without end.
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in together with you is a wonderful start.
ここから これから
From here, from now on,
Our Bright Parade Parade
ということで！
And with that!
RosaMiA アコースティックライブ始まりました！
The RosaMiA Acoustic Live has begun!
始まりましたー！イエーイ！
It has begun! Yay!
どうでしたかー？
How did you like it?
1曲目の...
Starting off...
1曲目からね
From the first song, right?
Our Bright Paradeから... なんかさ、こういう感じでこの曲歌ったことなかったから...
With "Our Bright Parade"... We've never sung this song in this style before, so...
そう！そうなの！
Yeah! Totally!
すごいドキドキしちゃった。
...my heart was pounding so fast!
ドキドキしながら...
While feeling our hearts race...
わかる。
I know, right?
三声になってましたね。
We were singing in three-part harmony!
はい。
Yeah.
なんか最後ポーズ決めるの忘れかけてたよね、ちょっと。
I think we almost forgot to strike the final pose at the end.
集中しすぎて
Because we were so focused!
すごい集中してた。歌に集中しすぎてちょっと焦ってたかも。
Super focused! I was so focused on the singing that I panicked a bit.
まぁそんなこともありながらね。
Well, things like that happen too!
はい、はい。
Yeah, yeah!
あ、もう既に... え？なんと
Ah, already... Huh? Believe it or not...
えー、こちら、ハッシュタグのトレンドで3位に入ってるらしい！
Um, apparently our hashtag is trending at #3!
何ー？！えー！すごい！ありがとー！
What?! Wow! Amazing! Thank you!
ありがとー！
Thank you so much!
あ、とりあえず、ちょっと自己紹介から...
First off, let's do our introductions...
そうですね、自己紹介しましょう！
That's right, let's introduce ourselves!
ちょっと、よろしくお願いします。
Please treat us well.
では、自己紹介させていただきます。
Now then, I'll go ahead and introduce myself.
RosaMiaの「ロー」担当、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタール...
In charge of the "Ro" in RosaMia, I'm Aki Rosenthal, aka AkiRose...
です！ハロハロハロ〜、アローナ〜！
...here! Hello, hello, hello~, Aloha~!
イエ〜イ！そして！
Yay! And next!
はーい！RosaMiaの「み」担当、長女の狼神ミオです！よろしくお願いしまーす！
Hi! In charge of the "Mi" in RosaMia, I'm the oldest sister, Mio Ookami! Pleased to meet you!
イェーイ！そして！
Yay! And next!
はい！RosaMiaの「あ」担当、末っ子のAZKiです！あずきん！よろしくお願いしまーす！
Yes! In charge of the "A" in RosaMia, I'm the youngest sister, AZKi! Azukin! Pleased to meet you!
なんか生き生きとさ、末っ子してるんだよな、この空間にいると。
You really come alive playing the youngest sister when you're here.
この3人だとね！末っ子でいられる！
With the three of us, I get to be the youngest!
お幸せです、ありがとうございます。
I'm so happy, thank you!
そうだ、長女...
That's right, the oldest...
長女、次女、末っ子！
Oldest, middle, youngest!
3姉妹でやらせていただいております！
We're doing this as three sisters!
ということでね、この3人でRosaMiaというグループをやらせていただいているんですけれども、
So the three of us form this group called RosaMia, but...
なんとですね、このRosaMiaでライブをするのは今回初めてということで！
Believe it or not, this is our very first time performing live as RosaMia!
そうなんです！
That's right!
しかも、あの、生歌唱のライブということでね、3人でいっぱい練習しましたね！
And since it's a live singing performance, the three of us practiced a lot!
練習しました！合宿のように！
We sure did! Just like a training camp!
頑張ったね！もう部活みたいでさ、楽しかった！
We worked hard! It felt like a school club, it was so fun!
そうだね、部活だったら合唱部みたいな感じだね。
Right, if it were a club, it'd be like the choir club.
たくさん練習したのでね、たくさん練習した1曲目どうでしたでしょうか？
We practiced a ton, so how did you like that first song we practiced so hard for?
どうでしたか？いや、一番難しいまであるか？
How was it? Or was it maybe the hardest one?
いや、そんなことはない！
No, no way!
そんなことはなかった、でもかなり難しい方ではあった。
It wasn't quite that bad, but it definitely was on the difficult side.
パート分けでしたよね。
It was the harmony split, right?
いや、そうだね！パート分けが難しかったかも。
Yeah, that's true! Splitting up the vocal parts was probably tough.
というわけで、トレンドが3位にもう入ってるという情報ですが...
Anyway, we got word that we're already trending at #3, but...
はい！ハッシュタグこちらとなっておりまーす！
Yes! Here is our hashtag!
「RosaMiaアコースティックライブ」というタグで、
With the hashtag "#RosaMiaAcousticLive,"
皆さんどしどしXでポストしてくださいねー！よろしくお願いします！
everyone please post away on X! We appreciate it!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
後であのエゴサするので、頑張ったのでね。
I'll be vanity-searching later, since we worked so hard.
応援だったりとか感想とかをつけていっぱいね、盛り上げてくれたら！
If you could hype it up with your cheers and impressions...!
見たい見たい！まだ知らない人にも届けたいですよね！
I want to see them! We want to reach people who don't know us yet, too!
はい！お願いします！
Yes! Please do!
今2位になってるよって！
They're saying we're #2 now!
え？！上がってる！すごすぎる！
What?! It went up! That's incredible!
ありがとうございます！ぜひぜひいっぱいポストしてねー！
Thank you so much! Please keep posting lots!
ねー！
Yeah~!
というわけでですね、はぁ〜...
So then, phew~...
どんどん行っちゃうんですか、これ？それとも永遠にここでトークしてるんですか？
Should we keep moving forward, or just keep chatting here forever?
え、ちょっとさ... お水飲む？お水飲もうかな！
Well, hey... / Drink some water? / Maybe I'll have some water!
ちょっと一瞬お水飲もう！
Let's drink some water for a second!
一瞬お水を飲ませてくださいね。
Please let us have a quick drink of water.
お水美味しい、美味しい。
Water is so tasty, so good.
はぁ〜... いや、一瞬お水飲ませてくださいとか言いつつ...
Phew... Saying "let us have a drink of water," but...
次は、もうそろそろ...
Next up, pretty soon...
次の曲行っちゃいますか？行っちゃいます？
Shall we move to the next song? Shall we?
はい！というわけで次の曲は、ウチとアキちゃんの、お、2人ということで！
Yes! So the next song will be by me and Aki-chan, the two of us!
こっから2人ずつ歌っていくんですね！
From here on, you'll be singing in pairs, right?
そうなんです！じゃあ2人は準備お願いします！
That's right! Then please go ahead and get ready, you two!
はい、AZKiちゃんにもね、お水飲んでもらったところ恐縮なんですけれども、MCを託したいと...
Yes, so sorry right after you drank water, AZKi-chan, but we'd like to leave the MC to you...
はい、2人がね、今ね、準備しておりますので...
Sure! While the two of them are getting ready...
助かる〜！はーい！みんなー！RosaMiaのアコースティックライブ来てくれてありがとうー！
Thanks so much~! Hi everyone~! Thank you all for coming to RosaMia's acoustic live!
1曲目いかがでしたか？「Our Bright Parade」！
How did you like our first song, "Our Bright Parade"?
今回ね、ぜひアレンジにも注目していただきたいなと、
This time, I'd really love for you to pay attention to the arrangement,
ちょっといつもとね、違うオシャレなアレンジになっておりますので、
because it's a stylish arrangement that's a bit different from the original.
そこもね、それと合わせて3人のハーモニーを聴いていただけたらなと思います！
Combined with that, I hope you'll enjoy listening to our three-part harmony!
おっ、というところで、2人が準備できたみたいなので！
Oh, and with that, looks like the two of them are ready!
はい！できました！
Yes! We're ready!
いいですか？はい、聴いていただきましょう。「JANE DOE」
Are you ready? All right, please listen to "JANE DOE."
JANE DOE / 作詞・作曲：米津玄師
[Song: JANE DOE / Lyrics & Music: Kenshi Yonezu]
うーん
Mmm...
まるでこの世界で 二人だけみたいだね
It's almost as if we're the only two left in this world.
なんて少しだけ 夢をみてしまっただけ
Or perhaps I was just dreaming for a little while.
爪先に月明かり 花束の香り
Moonlight on our tiptoes, the scent of a bouquet,
指に触れる指
fingers gently touching fingers.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ 何もかも
Goodbye, I have to go now, leaving everything...
忘れて...
Forget everything...
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot over shattered glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
with every painful step, blood flows and drips down.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those crimson footprints...
会いに来て
and come see me.
錆びたプールに放たれてく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusted pool,
靴箱の中 隠した林檎
an apple hidden inside a shoebox.
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡
Scars lingering on your withered skin,
犬のように泳いだ迷子
a lost child swimming like a dog.
どこにいるの (ここにいるよ)
Where are you? (I'm right here)
何をしてるの (ずっと見てるよ)
What are you doing? (I've been watching you all along)
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
側にいてよ 遊びに行こうよ
Stay by my side, let's go play.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot over shattered glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
with every painful step, blood flows and drips down.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those crimson footprints...
会いに来て
and come see me.
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It felt as if we were the only two in this world,
なんて少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
but it was nothing more than a fleeting dream.
はーい、ふー、歌いきったー！
Phew, we sang it all the way through!
いや、やっぱ素敵な曲だね。
Man, that really is a wonderful song, isn't it?
本当だね。
It really is.
というわけで、アキちゃんとウチの「JANE DOE」でしたー！
And so, that was "JANE DOE" by Aki-chan and me!
わー！ めっちゃ素敵ー！
Yay! That was so wonderful!
ありがとうー！ ありがとう！
Thank you so much!
はぁ、ちょっと緊張した。 / 緊張したね。
Phew, I got a little nervous. / We were nervous, weren't we?
そんなこと感じさせない歌声でしたよ、ほんと。
Your singing didn't show it at all, seriously!
本当？ 本当？ / 良かったー。
Really? Really? / Glad to hear that~
なんかこの曲は、まあ2人ずつね、これから歌っていくんだろうな、みたいなうっすら思ってるかもしれないんですけど、
You might vaguely guess we'll keep singing in pairs like this, but...
え、どうですか？ どこが難しかったですか？ この曲は。
So, how was it? Which part was the hardest in this song?
えー、でもやっぱハモリがさ、原曲より少し多めにこうハモる場所を作っていって、
Well, we added more harmonies than the original song,
で、そこのやっぱ掛け合いとか、こう合わせるみたいなのとかを...
so getting the call-and-response and syncing our timing right...
呼吸感とか？ / うんうん。
Like breathing together? / Yeah, yeah.
アキちゃんが多分以前アキちゃんのライブでJANE DOEやってるからかわかんないけど、ほぼ完璧だったわけ、ハモリが！
Aki-chan did "JANE DOE" before at her solo live, so her harmonies were almost flawless!
え、そんなことないよ！
No way, that's not true!
ほぼ最初から出来上がってて、練習しなきゃいけないのウチだったわけ！
She was ready from the start, so I was the one who had to practice hard!
ウチだったわけ？ / アキロゼの生誕祭でね。
You were the one? / At Akirose's birthday live, right?
そう、みおちゃんパートのメロディを歌わせてもらったことがあって。
Right, I sang Mio-chan's melody part back then,
で、こっちの米津さんパートは初挑戦だったんだけど、雰囲気とかは入ってたから。
so while Yonezu-san's part was new to me, I already had the feel of it down.
いや、分かってたからもう最初からほぼ完璧で。
See? Since she already knew it, she was basically perfect from day one.
いやいや、そんなことないですよ。 / ウチは「あわわ、あわわ」ってしてて。
No, not at all! / While I was panicking like "ah wah wah"!
めちゃくちゃ素敵なね、声の伸びだったよ。
Your vocal extension was absolutely amazing!
ハモれてすごい楽しかったー！
It was so much fun harmonizing with you!
ちょっと緊張したけどかなりアキちゃんのハーモニーに助けられたというか、やっぱハモリ上手いからさ、アキちゃん！
I was nervous, but Aki-chan's harmonies saved me. You're so good at harmonizing!
上手いのよ、アキちゃんはね！ / ありがとうございます。
She really is great at it! / Thank you very much.
天性のハモリスト。 / ハモリ好きだもんね、ハモリスト！
A natural-born harmonist. / You love harmonizing, don't you? A harmonist!
まだまだ精進させていただきますが。 / いやいやいや。
I still have much to learn, but... / No, no.
じゃあ、まあそろそろあれですかね？
Well then, is it about time for that?
え、もう行っちゃうんですか？！ まだ引っ張って話すなら漫才始めますけど！
Wait, are you leaving already?! If you stall any longer, we'll start a comedy routine!
漫才始まっちゃう！
A comedy routine is gonna break out!
まあそろそろね、次の準備ということで、みおちゃんとAZKiちゃんに歌ってもらうので、アキロゼはあちらの方に。
Well, it's time to prep for the next song. Mio-chan and AZKi-chan will be singing, so Akirose will head over there.
ドキドキ。
I'm so thrilled!
よいしょっと
Here we go.
頑張ろう、あずちゃん / 頑張ろうね
Let's do our best, Azu-chan. / Let's do our best!
緊張するよ、ちょっと
I'm a little nervous.
緊張するね
So nervous, right?
ちょっとお水飲もうかな
I think I'll drink some water.
お水飲んでね、お水飲んで
Go ahead and drink some water.
二人ともお水飲んでもらって
While the two of them get some water...
じゃあその間にアキロゼ、ちょっとコメントをあれしようかな
In the meantime, let me check the comments!
うん、うん、うん、うん
Let's see...
いや「草」っていう文字がすごくあの、黄緑で目立って拾いやすいなと...
The "lol" comments really stand out in lime green and are easy to catch...
あ、なんですけど、
Ah, wait, speaking of which...
ウチらの自作です / あれ、そうなの？
We made those ourselves. / Oh, really?
え、かわいいスタンプ！
Aw, that's such a cute stamp!
いや、でもね、こうやってみんなもなんか結構「待ってたよ」「RosaMiAのライブ嬉しい」っていう
Well, I've seen so many comments like, "We've been waiting for this!" and "So happy for RosaMiA's live!"
声もあの、見てたので、すごいありがとうございます。
Thank you all so very much!
ちょっと緊張して、初挑戦なのでね、
They're a bit nervous since this is their first attempt at this,
あの色々と頑張るっていうことでやってますので、応援よろしくお願いします。
so they're putting everything into it. Please give them your support!
では、二人は準備できたみたいなので、
Now, looks like they're both ready,
次の曲、聴いていただきましょう。
so let's listen to the next song.
『夜光通信』
"Nightlight Communication."
聴こえますか
Can you hear me?
夜光通信
[Song: Nightlight Communication]
Hello Hello 聴こえますか
Hello, hello, can you hear me?
そっちは何年？
What year is it over there?
正しくわかりあう手段は
A way to truly understand each other...
ひとつじゃないさ
...isn't just one.
漂う時間はどこへ行くのか
Where does drifting time go?
さよならはいつ誰が決めるの
When and who decides goodbyes?
その手に触れようと願ってる
I'm wishing to touch that hand of yours
本当さ
I really am.
永遠の夜行 君に歌う
Singing to you through this eternal night travel
世界中が君に意地悪でも
Even if the whole world is cruel to you,
思い出して 覚えていて
Remember, keep it in mind,
瞼の裏 ずっとまた会えるからね
Behind your eyelids, we can always meet again.
穏やかに 健やかに
Gently, serenely,
奏でるブーケ 君だって私だって
a bouquet of music—for both you and me.
消えるのは 言葉だけ
The only things that fade are words.
ふんわり君を抱きしめてあげるからね
I'll softly embrace you,
泣かないで
so please don't cry.
延々と続く今日は
This endlessly continuing today...
雪原のようで
...is like a snowy plain,
突然の幸せまでも
dazzling and concealing...
眩ませるんだ
...even sudden happiness.
忘れないで どこへだって
Never forget, wherever you may be,
繋がる回線
the line is connected.
寂しい宇宙とオレンジの公園
A lonely universe and an orange park,
慕わしい心の限りを
with all my longing heart,
歌を
I send this song.
永遠の夜行 届くよね
This eternal night travel, it reaches you, right?
幻想よりも優しい形のまま
Remaining in a shape gentler than illusions.
濡れそぼる その頬を
Those drenched cheeks of yours,
こっそり撫でて 乾かしてあげるからね
I will secretly stroke and dry them for you.
何度だって
Time and time again.
永遠の夜行 虚空に歌う
Singing into the void on an eternal night travel
逢いたいよ 消えたくなんてないよ
I want to see you; I don't want to disappear.
思い出して 覚えていて
Remember, keep it in mind:
今ここで笑いあったことを
how we smiled together right here.
永遠の夜行 君に歌う
Singing to you through this eternal night travel
世界中が君に意地悪でも
Even if the whole world is cruel to you,
思い出して 覚えていて
Remember, keep it in mind,
瞼の裏 ずっとまた会えるからね
Behind your eyelids, we can always meet again.
さよならは さよならは
A goodbye, a goodbye...
ねえ 誰が決めるもの？
...tell me, who decides that?
消えるのは 言葉...
The only things that fade are words...
ねえ
Hey...
ふわり君を抱きしめてあげるからね
I'll gently embrace you, so...
泣かないで
Don't cry.
というわけで！
And with that!
『夜光通信』歌わせていただきました！
We performed "Yakou Tsuushin"!
『夜光通信』！ありがとうございますー！
"Yakou Tsuushin"! Thank you so much!
いやー、すごくね、素敵で聴き入ってたんですけど...
Man, it was so wonderful, I was completely mesmerized, but...
あの、なんと嬉しいお知らせが入ってまして...
You know, we've actually received some wonderful news!
何ですか？何ですか？
What is it? What is it?
あの、トレンド1位を、こちら！
Look at this, we reached #1 on trending!
ハッシュタグで獲得いたしましたー！
Our hashtag reached the top spot!
やったー！
Yay!
みんなのおかげ！
It's all thanks to everyone!
みんなのおかげ。RosaMiAの名を轟かせて...
Thanks to everyone. Spreading the name of RosaMiA...
嬉しいねー！日曜日なのにすごい！
I'm so happy! That's amazing for a Sunday!
嬉しい！ありがとー、みんな！
I'm so glad! Thank you, everyone!
みんなのコメントでも、アコースティックバージョンのアレンジがすごいっていうコメントもたくさんあったし...
There were also tons of comments saying how amazing the acoustic arrangement was...
やっぱりハーモニーがすごく綺麗って、みんな言ってくれてて...
and everyone said the harmonies were so beautiful...
嬉しいなー！
That makes me so happy!
でも上手にできたよねー！
We really pulled it off well, didn't we!
できたよね！うん、できたできた！
We totally did! Yeah, we did it!
なんかさ、向かい合って歌ってるとことか、ぞくぞくしたもんね！
Like, when you two were singing face-to-face, it gave me goosebumps!
まあ実はですね、こちらの選曲はAZちゃんがしてくれまして。
Well actually, AZ-chan was the one who chose this song.
今回はミオちゃんの枠でやらせていただくということもあり、僭越ながら、
Since we're doing this on Mio-chan's channel, if I may say so myself,
やはりもうこの曲大好きすぎて、ミオちゃんの『夜光通信』を...
I just love this song so much, Mio-chan's "Yakou Tsuushin"...
なんか歌いまくっててすみませんっていう気持ちなんですけど...
I feel like, "I'm sorry for singing it all the time," but...
嬉しいんですけどね、なんか本人よりも歌ってるという噂がある...
I'm happy about it, though there's a rumor you sing it more than the original singer...
なんか言われてる！まずい！
People are saying that?! Oh no!
印象的にね。「あれ？AZKiちゃん今日も歌ってる？」って...
Just impression-wise. Like, "Wait, is AZKi-chan singing it today too?"...
めっちゃ嬉しいんだけどね、本当に。
I'm super happy about it though, really.
いやでも、今回のアコースティックアレンジでより曲の良さも伝わったんじゃないかなと。
No, but I think this acoustic arrangement brought out the beauty of the song even more.
エモさがね！より強調されてたよねー！
The emotional feel was highlighted even more!
あー、良かったー！本当に。
Ah, that was so good! Truly.
はい、聴き入りました。
Yes, I was completely drawn in.
みんな良かったかなー？感想お願いします！
Did everyone enjoy it? Please let us know your thoughts!
ね、お願いしますー。
Yes, please do!
じゃあ、ちょゆ...ちょい、ちょゆーことで...
Well then, so-so-so-so with that...
ここでね、アキが入ってきたということは...
Now, since Aki came on stage...
AZちゃんとアキちゃんの2人で歌っちゃうんじゃないですか？
does that mean AZ-chan and Aki-chan are going to sing as a duo?!
歌っちゃいます！はーい！
We sure will! Yay!
あ、ちょっとね、その間にうちはMCやるからさ。
Ah, I'll handle the MC in the meantime.
はい、ということでね、大神ミオチャンネルの大神ミオです！よろしくお願いします！
Alright, so I'm Ookami Mio from the Ookami Mio Channel! Nice to have you here!
こんばんみぉーん！
Good evening, Mion!
うち、うち、うちだよー！大神ミオだよー！
It's me, me, it's me! Ookami Mio! Haven't done that yet tonight.
ありがとう、助かるー！
Thank you, appreciate it!
うん、休憩してないんだよな、あまり。茶々入れてんだよなー。
Yeah, I haven't really been taking a break. I keep chiming in.
はい、というわけでね、皆さんもコメントいっぱいありがとうございます！
Alright, so thank you all so much for all the comments!
そしてRosaMiAアコースティックライブで、トレンド1位にもしていただいたということで、
And thanks to everyone, the RosaMiA acoustic live reached #1 on trending,
後で感想を見るのめっちゃ楽しみにしてます！
so I'm really looking forward to reading your impressions later!
というわけで、準備も良さそうなので...
And with that, looks like they're ready, so...
そろそろ聴いていただきましょうか。皆さん。
shall we have you listen now, everyone?
では、皆さんの準備はいいですか？
Now, is everyone ready?
聴いていただきましょう。
Please listen to...
『月のワルツ』
"Tsuki no Waltz."
こんなに月が青い夜は 不思議なことが起きるよ
On a night when the moon is so blue, strange things happen.
どこか深い森の中で さまよう私
Wandering in the depths of a forest somewhere...
タキシード姿のうさぎが来て ワインはいかがとテーブルへ
A rabbit in a tuxedo approaches, offering wine at the table.
真っ赤なキノコの傘の下で 踊りが始まる
Beneath the cap of a bright red mushroom, the dance begins.
あなたは...
You are...
どこにいるの
Where are you,
時間の国の迷子
lost child in the land of time?
帰り道がわからないの
I don't know the way back home,
待てど待てど
no matter how long I wait...
眠れぬこの魂は
This sleepless soul
あなたを探し森の中
searches for you within the forest.
シャンドラマハルの王子様が
The prince of Chandra Mahal
膝まずいてワルツ誘う
kneels and invites me to a waltz.
睫の長い蝶々たちが
The long-lashed butterflies,
シフォンのドレスでひらひらと
fluttering lightly in chiffon dresses;
虹色のタイツの甲虫は
the beetles in iridescent tights,
剣のダンス
dance with their swords.
求めるものはなに？
What is it that you seek?
幻惑のラビリンス
The labyrinth of illusions...
ミルク色の霧の彼方
Beyond the milky-colored mist,
確かな愛がほしい
I yearn for a love that is certain.
冷たいこの爪先を
These cold toes of mine,
白鳥の羽でくるんで
wrap them in swan feathers.
シャンドラマハルの王子様は
The prince of Chandra Mahal
あなたに似た瞳で笑う
smiles with eyes just like yours.
満ちては欠ける
Waxing and waning,
空を行く
traveling across the sky,
神秘の船
a vessel of mystery.
変わらないものなど無いと
"Nothing stays unchanged forever,"
語りかけて
whispering to me,
くるるよ
revolving round and round.
こんなに月が青い夜は
On a night when the moon is this blue,
不思議なことが起きるよ
mysterious things happen.
どこか見知らぬ森の中で
Somewhere within an unfamiliar forest,
彷徨う私
here I wander.
こんなに月が青い夜は
On a night when the moon is this blue,
不思議なことが起きるよ
mysterious things happen.
愛する事は信じること
To love is to believe.
いつかその胸に抱かれ
Someday, embraced in those arms,
眠った夢を見る
I dream of falling asleep.
はーい！ということで
All right! And with that...
『月のワルツ』でした！
That was "Tsuki no Waltz"!
すごく良かったよ！
That was so great!
『月のワルツ』でした！
That was "Tsuki no Waltz"!
素晴らしかった！
It was wonderful!
はぁ～、大変だった～
Whew, that was tough~
いや、あのさぁ、うちはさ、
Well, you know, for me,
やっぱ最初から、2人が練習してるときから知ってるんだけど、
since I've known and watched you two practicing right from the start,
今日、完成した感ある！
it feels like you really perfected it today!
え、本当に？！
Really?!
えー、嬉しい！
Yay, I'm so happy!
あるよ！本当に！
You really did! Truly!
うわ、泣きそう...
Aw, I'm gonna cry...
声、上手くなった？
Did our singing improve?
えー、嬉しい！やったー！
Yay, so glad! We did it!
綺麗だった～
It sounded so beautiful~
いや～、でもさ、緊張したよね？
Whew, but still, you were nervous, right?
緊張したね！
We sure were!
ハモリでさ、入るところがいつもドキドキするってAZKiちゃん言ってたよね。
AZKi-chan was saying how coming in for the harmony always gets her heart racing.
そう！今回アキちゃんメインでAZKiがハモリで入らせてもらっているんですけれども、
Yeah! This time, Aki-chan was on main vocal while I did the harmony, but...
このハモリが「うっ、いや～！」みたいな...
that harmony entry felt so "Ugh, oh no~!"...
だから練習した！
That's why we practiced!
記憶？
In your memories?
いやめっちゃ練習したもんね！
Yeah, we practiced like crazy, after all!
確かに～
True~
いやもう本当に偉いな～って、なんか感動しちゃった！
Man, you did so well, it actually moved me!
えー！成長したや？
Aww! Did we grow?
素晴らしいなあって。
It was just wonderful.
いや、いいハーモニーでしたね～。
Yeah, it was a lovely harmony~.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
はぁ～、本当にね。
Phew, really.
でもなんか、ここで満足しちゃいけませんよ。
But you know, we can't be satisfied just yet.
ここで満足しちゃ、まだ早いですよ！まだ3人でさ、1曲しか歌ってないから。
Being satisfied now is way too early! The three of us have only sung one song together so far!
確かに！
True!
え、確かに！RosaMiAなのに！
Yeah, true! Even though we're RosaMiA!
そうだよ！こっからね！
Exactly! From here on!
そうだね。
Right.
みんなもまだまだ...え、もうね？
Everyone is still... wait, already?
次何？次何？
What's next? What's next?
次何でしょう？ なってましたよ
"I wonder what's next?" / "They were asking!"
いや、そうだよね。何だろうね。
Yeah, really. I wonder what it is.
で、もう本当にね、ステージも綺麗で。なんかさっき...
And really, the stage is so pretty too. Earlier...
なんか出てましたよね？ / そうなの！
Something was showing on screen, right? / That's right!
さっきね、今無くなっちゃったけどさ。
Yeah, it's gone now though.
でもね、ちゃんと「今日も月が綺麗ですね」って言ってくれてたから、コメントでも。
But everyone was saying, "The moon is beautiful tonight," in the comments too.
『月ノワルツ』... あら！ / あのイメージでね。
From "Tsuki no Waltz"... Oh! / Following that image, yeah.
そうなんです。月の破片に乗らせてもらいまして。
That's right. We got to ride on a fragment of the moon.
ここはなんか宇宙空間ですかね？
Is this space we're in now?
宇宙空間？ うん、すごいステージだ。綺麗だなあ。
Space? Yeah, it's an amazing stage. So beautiful.
じゃあちょっとね、そろそろ次の曲行っちゃいます？
Well then, shall we head on to the next song?
行っちゃう？
Shall we?
やばい、ちょっと緊張してお水... お水飲みたいかも。
Oh no, I'm getting a bit nervous, water... / I might want some water too.
緊張してきた。緊張してきた。
I'm getting nervous. So nervous!
大丈夫かな？ / よいしょ、よいしょ。
Are you alright? / All right, all right.
いや、次の曲も結構ね、気合いがいるよね。
Well, the next song takes quite a lot of focus, right?
はい。気合いを入れまして。
Yes. Getting pumped up.
いります！ 気合いいります！
It really does! We need that energy!
おっ！ なんと、ステージがちょっと変わりまして。
Oh! Wow, the stage changed a bit.
このキューブはなんかちょっと懐かしくないですか？ 見覚えがある！
Doesn't this cube feel kind of familiar? / I recognize it!
実はアキロゼの生誕祭で2人に来てもらって、最初に3人で歌わせてもらった時に...
Actually, when I invited you two to my birthday live and we sang together as a trio for the first time...
こういうなんかキューブ状のステージで歌わせてもらったんだけど...
...we sang on a cube-shaped stage just like this, and...
なんかそれをね、ちょっと彷彿とさせるっていうか。再現していただいて。
It kind of brings that back, doesn't it? They recreated it for us.
『君の銀の庭』を歌ったという記憶があります。 / そう！
I remember we sang "Kimi no Gin no Niwa." / That's right!
え、それ歌うんですか？ / えー！？ そんな！
Wait, are we singing that? / What?! No way!
何歌うんだろうね？ そんな思い出もありますけれども。
I wonder what we're singing? We have those memories too, but...
そうなんですよ。まだ聴いてない人はよかったら聴いてみてください。
That's right. If you haven't heard it yet, please check it out.
アキちゃんのチャンネルであがってますね。そっちもすごく頑張ったんで。
It's up on Aki-chan's channel. We worked really hard on that too.
そうなんです。というわけで。
That's right. And so...
ここからなんと、2曲連続で歌っていきます。
From here on, we're going to sing two songs back-to-back!
ちょっと音を合わせさせてくださいね。難しい曲なので。歌で始まりますからね。
Let us tune our pitch for a moment. It's a difficult song, starting right with the vocals.
えー
Ah...
Every day I listen to my heart
ひとりじゃない
I am not alone
深い胸の奥で つながってる
Deep within my chest, we are connected
果てしない時を越えて
Crossing through endless time,
輝く星が
the shining stars
出会えた奇跡
teach me the miracle
教えてくれる
of our encounter.
Every day I listen to my heart
ひとりじゃない
I am not alone
この空の御胸に
Held closely
抱かれて
in the embrace of this sky.
Woh yeah... Ooh yeah...
Woah yeah... Ooh yeah...
私のこの両手で
With these hands of mine,
何ができるの？
what can I do?
痛みに触れさせて
Let me touch the pain,
そっと目を閉じて
and gently close my eyes.
夢を失うよりも
Rather than losing a dream,
悲しいことは
the saddest thing of all
自分を信じて あげられないこと
is being unable to believe in yourself.
愛を学ぶために
In order to learn love,
孤独があるなら
if loneliness must exist,
意味のないことなど
then there is nothing without meaning...
孤独にはしない
I will never leave you lonely.
心の静寂に
In the stillness of your heart,
耳を澄まして
listen closely.
私を呼んだなら
If you call out to me,
どこへでも行くわ
I will go anywhere.
あなたのその涙
Let those tears of yours
私のものに
become mine.
今は自分を
For now, hold yourself close
抱きしめて
in a gentle embrace,
命のぬくもり
and feel the warmth
感じて
of life itself.
私たちは誰も
None of us
ひとりじゃない
are ever truly alone.
ありのままでずっと
Just as you are,
愛されている
you are always loved.
望むように生きて
Live as you wish,
輝く未来を
and for that radiant future,
いつまでも歌うわ
I will keep on singing forever,
あなたのために
just for you.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
記憶をたどり
tracing back your memories,
優しさと夢の源へ
to the source of gentleness and dreams.
もう一度 星にひかれ
Drawn to the stars once more
生まれるために
so that you may be reborn,
魂のルフラン
refrain of the soul.
包まれた素肌が
Your bare skin, wrapped,
時のなかで 静かにふるえてる
trembles quietly within time.
命の行方を 問いかけるように
As if asking where life is bound,
指先は私をもとめる
your fingertips reach out for me.
抱きしめてた運命のあなたは
You, my destined love whom I embraced,
季節に咲く まるではかない花
are like a fleeting flower blooming in season.
希望のにおいを 胸に残して
Leaving the scent of hope in my heart,
散り急ぐ 鮮やかな...
you hasten to scatter in brilliance...
...な姿で
...in your vivid form.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
生まれる前に
before your birth,
あなたが過ごした 大地へと
back to the earth where you once lived.
この手に還りなさい
Return into these arms,
めぐり逢うため
so that we may meet again.
奇跡は起こるよ 何度でも
Miracles will happen again and again.
魂のルフラン
It's the soul's refrain.
祈るように まぶた閉じたときに
When I close my eyes as if in prayer,
世界はただ 闇の底に消える
the world simply vanishes into the depths of darkness.
それでも鼓動は また動きだす
Yet even so, my heartbeat starts to pulse again,
限りある永遠を探して
searching for a finite eternity.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
記憶をたどり
tracing your memories,
優しさと夢の源へと
back to the source of gentleness and dreams.
あなたも還りなさい
You, too, must return,
愛しあうため
so that we may love one another.
心も体もくりかえす
Heart and body repeat anew.
魂のルフラン
It's the soul's refrain.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
生まれる前に
before your birth,
あなたが過ごした 大地へと
back to the earth where you once lived.
この手に還りなさい
Return into these arms,
めぐり逢うため
so that we may meet again.
奇跡は起こるよ 何度でも
Miracles will happen again and again.
魂のルフラン
It's the soul's refrain.
ということで
And with that...
はい、2曲連続で聴いていただきました！
Yes, you just heard two songs back to back!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much!
分かってるよ！分かってるよ！
We know, we know!
自分が一番分かってるよね！
You know best of all!
一緒に振り向いたら、そのままなんか安心しちゃったｗ
When we turned around together, I just felt so relieved and relaxed!
ちょっとやばい、これアキちゃんもしかして忘れてるかもと思って、一瞬うちが歌おうか迷ったんだけど、でも...
I was like "Oh no, maybe Aki-chan forgot?" and wondered if I should sing, but...
と思い... / すみませんｗ
I thought... / I'm sorry!
でも途中から気づいたから！気づいたから良かった！
But you noticed halfway through! I'm glad you realized!
はい、ギリギリ！
Yeah, just in the nick of time!
セーフ！セーフ、セーフ！
Safe! Safe, totally safe!
もう1回やったっていいんじゃない？
Why not do it one more time?
やばいｗ もう1回やろっか？
Oh no haha. Should we do it again?
もう1回やったっていいよ！
We totally could do another take!
リテイクやばいｗ
A retake is crazy!
はあ〜
Phew~
まあでもね、皆さんすごくコメントの勢いがね、物語ってますよ。
But anyway, the excitement in the chat really says it all!
「すごくかっこよかったよ」って言ってくれてるよ！
They're saying "It was so cool!"
ありがたい！ありがとう！
We appreciate it! Thank you!
いやもう、これ、これが生の証明ですから！
Well, this is pure proof that it's 100% live!
確かにｗ 身を切って証明したねｗ
Exactly! You proved it at your own expense!
完全体はいつかまた...
The complete version will be for another time...
完全体はね！成長コンテンツだからさ！
That's right! It's growth content, after all!
いや一度もこの失敗さ、今までの練習でも一度もなかったのに！
But we never once made this mistake in all our rehearsals!
一度もなかった！どうした！？
Not even once! What happened?!
こんなことなかったのに！
That never happened before!
本番の魔物来たね、これ！
The stage gremlins showed up today!
本番の魔物が... 安心しちゃった、後ろ振り向いたらｗ
The stage gremlins... I just got so relieved when I turned around!
「あれ？」って。「全員、全員後ろ向いてる？」ってｗ
I was like, "Wait... is everyone facing backwards?"
「アキちゃん？」みたいなｗ
Like, "Aki-chan...?"
恥ずかしくて火が出てる、顔から！
My face is literally on fire from embarrassment!
すごかった、でもね。はい。
It was great though! Yes.
いやなんとかね、ここまでいっぱいに練習した曲を披露できて嬉しいなって思ってるんですけれども！
We're so glad we were able to perform the songs we practiced so hard for, but...
ここでですね、うちから、ちょっとお知らせというか、みんな知ってるんですけど...
Right here, I have a quick announcement... Well, everyone already knows, but...
なんと、大神ミオ誕生日記念グッズ、発売中でございますー！
Ookami Mio's Birthday Celebration Goods are now on sale!
バースデーお知らせ！こちらチェックしてみてくださーい！
Birthday announcement! Please be sure to check it out!
スカジャンとですね、こちらアクリルキーホルダーとなっておりますー！
We have a Sukajan jacket and acrylic keychains!
こちらですー。
Here they are~
え、こちら受注期間あと4日なので...
There are only 4 days left in the pre-order period, so...
もうすぐじゃん！
That's coming up soon!
終わるんです
...will be ending soon.
はい あの もしね 買ってなくて「やべ 忘れてた」って人はね あの ちょっと早めに買っていただけるとっていうところではございますー
So if you haven't bought it yet and go, "Shoot, I forgot!", please consider picking it up soon!
よろしくお願いしまーす
We'd really appreciate it!
はい！
All right!
というわけで まあ さらっとね あの お知らせしちゃったんですけど
So, while we casually slipped in that announcement...
はい もう一個ありますよね？
Yes. There's one more thing, right?
あ サムネイルに告知ありって...
Ah, the thumbnail mentioned an announcement...
書いてありましたけど
It was indeed written there, but...
今日は3人の告知が なんと...
Today, the three of us have an announcement that's...
なんですか？ あるんですよ！
What is it? We actually have one!
言っちゃっていいですか？ 言っちゃってー！ どうぞ！
Can I say it? Go ahead! Please do!
なんと！
Believe it or not!
RosaMiAの...
RosaMiA's...
ファーストシングルが！
very first single...
デジタルリリースされます！
will be digitally released!
イエーイ！
Yay!
タイトル「Blossom Sinfonia」でございますー
The title is "Blossom Sinfonia"!
オリジナル楽曲ですね！
It's our original song!
オリジナル楽曲なんですよ！なんと なんと なんと！
It's an original song! Can you believe it?!
我らのRosaMiAのファーストシングルということで
As RosaMiA's first single...
初めにふさわしいような 3人の声が咲き誇るようなね 楽曲に
it's a fitting track where our three voices bloom in full glory,
そして我らのRosaMiAロードも 咲き誇ってくれるように
and in hopes that our RosaMiA path will bloom vibrantly too,
そんな華やかな1曲目に...
it turned into such a gorgeous first song!
かなり華やかとなっておりますね
It really has become quite gorgeous, hasn't it?
大事に育てていきたいなと思ってる曲ですし
It's a song we want to treasure and nurture,
みんなにもね 愛される曲になっていってくれたらいいなと思っておりますので
and we hope it grows to be loved by everyone as well. So...
この後24時から
Starting from midnight tonight,
各配信サイトでダウンロードできますので
you can download it on various streaming platforms,
ぜひ！ぜひ聴いてくださいねー！
so please, definitely give it a listen!
てわけで！
So!
ま でも この曲どんな曲か気にな...
But still, you must be wondering what kind of song it is...
気になるよねー！ 「咲き誇るような」とだけ言われてね
You must be curious! Just hearing "blooming in full glory,"
どんな曲なんだろう？「華やか？」みたいな
you'd wonder, "What's it like? Is it flashy?"
わかんないかなーって思うんですけどね
I bet you can't really tell just from that.
みんな聴きたいよね？ 聴きたい！ 聴きたいか！
Everyone wants to hear it, right? We want to! You want to hear it?
みんなのコメントを読んでいます
I'm reading everyone's comments.
その間に水飲もうよ そうだね
Let's drink some water in the meantime. Good idea.
「イラストもいい」「ビジュいい」「ありがとう」「気になる」「マジで」「聴く」
"Illustration is nice," "Great visual," "Thank you," "Curious," "For real," "Gonna listen..."
「ホロドリ来るか」 え？ ホロドリスさん どうですか？
"Is HoloDori coming?" Huh? What do you say, HoloDori-san?
どうなんですか？ホロドリスさん
What do you think, HoloDori-san?
アキロゼも水を飲み... アキちゃん可愛い 水飲んできてね
Akirose is drinking water too... Aki-chan is so cute, go drink your water.
いや 気になるよねー！ 聴きたい！
But man, aren't you curious?! We wanna hear it!
ということでね なんとアズちゃん この後... お披露目しちゃうかもしれないという話！
So actually, AZ-chan might just... unveil it right after this!
これは最後まで見逃せない... 見逃せないってこと？！
That means you can't miss this till the very end... You can't miss it?!
うんうんうん！
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
てなわけでですね なんとこの後 生歌唱にて初お披露目させていただきますー！
That's right! We'll be debuting it right here, right now, with a live singing performance!
ハードル高くないですか？！ 心を落ち着けて...
Aren't we setting the bar a bit high?! Calm your heart...
いや みんなにね 1回説明しておきたいんですけど
No, but I really want to explain something to everyone first:
この曲 歌唱難易度がバチ高くてですね
the singing difficulty of this song is insanely high!
今まで歌ってきた歌の中で 多分一番の最難関歌となっております！
Out of all the songs we've sung so far, this is probably the hardest one!
そうです！
It truly is!
この曲いっちゃん最初に練習し始めたもんね
This was the very first song we started practicing, after all.
どの曲よりも 一番練習した 一番練習したけど
We practiced it more than any other song! We practiced the most, and yet...
それでもなお難しい！ かなり難しい！ 超難しい！
Even so, it's still hard! Really hard! Super hard!
そうなんですよ
It really is.
どんな曲なんだろうね
Wonder what kind of song it is!
これを聴いてね ハモリとか好きな人もいると思うから 「どうやって歌ってんだろう？」みたいな
For those who love harmonies, I think you'll wonder, "How on earth are they singing this?"
考察じゃないけど 細かいところまでね
Even if it's not deep analysis, paying attention to the fine details...
聴いていただけたら嬉しいです そうですね 待ってます！
We'd be glad if you listen for that! That's right, we're looking forward to it!
本日24時 この後デジタルリリースされる曲となります
This song will be digitally released right after this, at midnight tonight!
もういいですか？言っちゃって ちょっと順番があるでしょ！
Are we ready to perform it? Hold on, there's an order to follow!
順番があるでしょ 大丈夫？
There's an order! Are you okay?
アキロゼは大盤振る舞いよ なんか最初から...
Akirose is being so lavishly hasty from the get-go...
嘘でしょ？！ 大丈夫大丈夫 頑張って！
No way, really?! It's okay, you got this!
大丈夫だよー 心配しないでね
You'll be fine! Don't worry!
今までの練習の成果を発揮すればええねん 練習してきたもん！
Just show the results of all our practice! We practiced so much!
はい というわけで 行きますよ？
All right then, phew, are you ready?
それでは聴いてください
Now then, please listen.
せーの Blossom Sinfonia！
Ready, set... Blossom Sinfonia!
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
So that our song will reach you from afar,
今宵に怯える 私がいる
Here I am, trembling in the night,
それでも明日に 期待している
Yet still holding onto hope for tomorrow.
あの日に見つけた 奇跡の種
The seed of miracles found on that day...
いつでもそこには希望がある
There is always hope to be found.
暗くても
Even in the dark,
一筋射す
a single ray shines through,
明日への光へと手を伸ばしてる
and I reach my hand toward that light of tomorrow,
今でも
even now.
途切れないように 繋いできたから
Because we've kept connecting so nothing would break,
今芽吹き始めた未来があるの
there is a future beginning to sprout right now.
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
So that our song reaches you far away,
この先も紡ぐの
we will keep weaving it onward.
Ah...
大事に抱えた 希望の芽は
The sprout of hope held close to our hearts
弱く儚い それでもいい
is weak and fragile, but that's okay.
いつの日か 小さくても
Someday, even if small,
重なれば 鮮やかに染め上げられる世界を
if they come together, we can vividly paint the world.
信じた未来へ 歩いてきたから
Because we've walked toward the future we believed in,
今手を取り合える 仲間がいるの
we have friends here whose hands we can hold.
遠くのあなたの 手を握れるように
So that we can hold your hand far away,
花は今 色づく
the flowers now take on their colors.
不安でも (不安でも) 大丈夫と
Even when anxious, believing it will be okay,
挫けても (挫けても) 続けてきた
even when crushed, we kept pushing forward.
弱くてもいい 怖くてもいい
It's okay to be weak, it's okay to be afraid.
届けると決めたんだ 響き渡れ あなたへ
We decided to reach you—resound far and wide!
途切れないように 繋いできたから
Because we've kept connecting so nothing would break,
今鮮やかなほど 咲き誇る花
the flowers now bloom in vivid glory.
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
So that our song reaches you far away,
変わらないよ (ずっと) 何があっても (ずっと)
it will never change, no matter what happens.
あなたへと紡ぐの
We will keep weaving our song for you.
本日24時よりデジタルリリース！ぜひみんなRosaMiAの1stシングル聴いてね！
Digital release starts tonight at 24:00! Please listen to RosaMiA's 1st single, everyone!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
頑張った！頑張った！イェーイ！
We did our best! We did it! Yay!
告知あり
[Announcement]